arkservers.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - ARK: Survival Evolved Servers

* * *

Make sure to click here or visit http://arkservers.net/terms/ to read the full Terms of Service, which contains a copy of the Privacy Policy.

* * *

We may refer to our website (ARKServers.net) throughout this document as "us", "we", "our", "our website", "the website", "website", "site", "service", "services", "ARK Servers", "ARK: Survival Evolved Servers", "ARKServers.net" or other first person pronouns and the User, customer, guest, person, or entity as "you", "your", "users", "member", "members", "customer, "customers", or other first person pronouns. Users of our website are defined as any person accessing, using, viewing, reading, printing, or otherwise utilizing our website.  
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for this website, which applies solely to information collected by this website. This means that the privacy policy may not include all the information collected by third parties or other services used within this website (payments processors, ads, etc). This privacy policy may include information about the following:

 __What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it may be used, and with whom it may be shared  
__What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data as a registered user  
__How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information as a registered user

**Cookies.** This website (like most websites on the internet) uses web browser cookies. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Please note that some parts of our website may not function properly. If you don't know what cookies are, don't worry - they are actually a good thing! Websites use them for record keeping. For example, a member/login system that needs to remember you.  
Click here or visit http://arkservers.net/cookies/ to read more about what cookies are and how we use cookies on our website.

**Account Details.** This section details information collected about registered users. You are a "registered user" if you have ever previously registered or logged in from the login page, which may be found at http://arkservers.net/login/ or by clicking here. **For non-paying website users** \- we only collect your email address, I.P. address, and public data obtained from your I.P. address. **For our paying customers** \- we collect your first name, last name, and email address in order to uniquely identify each person in our database. We do not sell your name or email address in any way, shape, or form. We do not process any "real world" payments through our website - they are all handled by third-party payment processors. ARKServers.net and GameServerStats, LLC. accepts no liability whatsoever and is not responsible if the information that we store in our database gets stolen or taken. 

**Emails.** When registering for an account, we ask for an email along with it. We may use this email to contact you or notify you regarding notifications, new services/products, or other information. We do not sell this email to third parties. You can manage your settings for this email in the Control Panel (click here). By default we may send important emails like support replies, transactions, private messages, or website related maintenance/updates. You can optionally choose to publicly display this email on your profile. You can also choose to receive other emails, for example: a new comment being posted on your claimed server or notifications when a server is seen as offline. 

**Guests.** This section details information collected about guests. You are automatically a "guest" by accessing, using, viewing, reading, printing, installing, downloading any material from, or otherwise utilizing this website. Registered users are also guests, and this section also applies to them. We collect your web browser header information, I.P. address, and public data obtained from your I.P. address (like your geographical location or internet service provider information). We may also collect data that you type into text boxes or other inputs on the website, like the search box. We may also collect data on buttons or links that you click within our website. We do not intend to collect any sensitive data from this. The data we collect from guests is very basic information, and we cannot personally identify guests using the data collected. This means that we cannot verify your identity which in turn means we cannot provide nor remove the data if a guest would like to request us to do so. If you want control over your data, please become a registered user. 

**Sharing.** We may share some information with our partners, payment processors, or advertisers. This is usually not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. However, we may partner with another party to provide specific services to you. When the user (you) sign up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. ARKServers.net and GameServerStats, LLC. accepts no liability whatsoever and is not responsible if the information that we store in our database gets stolen or taken. 

**Google.** This website may utilize both Google Analytics and Google Adsense. Google is governed by its own privacy policy ( which can be found on their website at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/> ) that each user must read should they want to know the type of data Google collects and what they do with it. We do not provide any additional information to Google that they can't access themselves via their scripts. We may use, share, and/or publish the data Google provides - which could help improve the user's experience on our website. 

**PayPal.** If a paying customer chooses to use Paypal for payments, Paypal may also directly request further information from each customer for billing purposes, such as a physical address and credit card information (or other payment method information). Paypal is governed by its own privacy policy ( which can be found on their website on <http://paypal.com/> ) that each user should read when making any payments through Paypal and before entering any private information into a Paypal webpage, system, or protocol. Paypal may occasionally share the physical address of a user with us, but we do not intentionally collect or store this information from it. 

**Stripe.** If a paying customer chooses to use Stripe for payments, Stripe may also directly request further information from each customer for billing purposes, such as a physical address and credit card information (or other payment method information). Stripe is governed by its own privacy policy ( which can be found on their website on <https://stripe.com/> ) that each user should read when making any payments through Stripe and before entering any private information into a Stripe webpage, system, or protocol. Stripe may occasionally share the physical address of a user with us, but we do not intentionally collect or store this information from it. 

**Links.** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Access & Control Your Data.** Registered users may opt out of any future email contact from us at any time. As a registered user, you can easily change your email & control how we use it in your Control Panel (click here), and you can also do the following at any time by contacting us via creating a support ticket - just click here or visit http://arkservers.net/support/

 __See what data we have about you, if any  
__Change/correct any data we have about you  
__Have us delete any data we have about you  
__Express any concern you have about our use of your data  
__Disable your account from any further login

We do not collect enough information about guests that we need in order to verify your identity, so we cannot provide guests with the services in this section.  
The information we collect about guests is very basic information and we do not intend to collect any sensitive information from guests. 

**Policy Changes.** We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy and all updates will be posted on this page. This Privacy Policy was last changed on June 21, 2016. We may attempt to prompt _registered users/members_ of our website after changes when you are logged in ( which looks similar to this: <http://arkservers.net/tos_prompt.jpg> )
